Guide to the Committee of Twenty-One, Yale University, Records
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
Committee of Twenty-one, Yale University, records concerning the Yale Bowl
1912-1917
RU 511
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
1.5
(4 boxes)
The records consist of subscription correspondence, letter books, and ledgers of the Yale University Committee of Twenty-one documenting fundraising for the construction of the Yale Bowl.
Yale University. Committee of Twenty-one
General note
Forms part of Yale Record Group 38-A (YRG 38-A), Records documenting administration of Yale athletic and physical education programs.
Conditions Governing Access
The materials are open for research.
Arrangement
The records are arranged by record type.
Scope and Contents
The records consist of subscription correspondence, letter books, and ledgers of the Yale University Committee of Twenty-one documenting fundraising for the construction of the Yale Bowl.
Fund raising; Sports facilities; Stadiums; Yale Bowl (New Haven, Conn.); Yale University -- Buildings; Yale University -- Sports
- Records, 1912-1917; Accession 1935-A-014
  Scope and Contents
  Records regarding the financing and building of Yale Bowl.
  - Subscription correspondence
    - 1912 Oct-Dec (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - 1913 Jan-Jun (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - 1913 Jul-Dec (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - 1914 Jan-Mar (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - 1914 Apr-Jun (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - 1914 Jul-Dec (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - 1915 Jan-Dec (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - 1916 Jan-Dec (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - 1917 Jan-Dec (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Letter books
    - 1914 May 28 -1916 Apr 5 (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - 1916 Apr 6 -1918 May 2 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Financial Correspondence and Records
    - 1912 Jan-Dec (Box 2, Folder 12)
    - 1913 Jan-Jun (Box 2, Folder 13)
    - 1913 Jul-Dec (Box 2, Folder 14)
    - 1914 Jan-Mar (Box 3, Folder 15)
    - 1914 Apr-Jul (Box 3, Folder 16)
    - 1914 Aug-Dec (Box 3, Folder 17)
    - 1915 Jan-Apr (Box 3, Folder 18)
    - 1915 May-Dec (Box 3, Folder 19)
    - 1916 Jan-Dec (Box 3, Folder 20)
    - 1917 Jan-Dec (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Subscription lists and miscellaneous records, [1912-1917?] (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - Ledgers
    - 1912 May -1913 Jun (Box 4, Folder 23)
    - 1912 Jun - 1913 Aug (Box 4, Folder 24)
    - 1915 Feb -1917 Aug (Box 4, Folder 25)